{
    "name": "Mohammad's workroom",
    "decks": [
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 0,
                    "correctTimes": 0,
                    "question": "Q1B",
                    "answer": "A1",
                    "mastery": false
                },
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 0,
                    "correctTimes": 0,
                    "question": "Q2B",
                    "answer": "A2",
                    "mastery": false
                }
            ],
            "subject": "BIOL"
        },
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 0,
                    "correctTimes": 0,
                    "question": "Q1C",
                    "answer": "A1",
                    "mastery": false
                },
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 0,
                    "correctTimes": 0,
                    "question": "H?",
                    "answer": "Hydrogen",
                    "mastery": false
                }
            ],
            "subject": "CHEM"
        },
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 0,
                    "correctTimes": 5,
                    "question": "Q1E",
                    "answer": "A1",
                    "mastery": false
                },
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 10,
                    "correctTimes": 0,
                    "question": "Q2E",
                    "answer": "A2",
                    "mastery": false
                }
            ],
            "subject": "ENGL"
        },
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 2,
                    "correctTimes": 3,
                    "question": "Q1M",
                    "answer": "A1",
                    "mastery": false
                },
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 0,
                    "correctTimes": 5,
                    "question": "Q2M",
                    "answer": "A2",
                    "mastery": false
                },
                {
                    "incorrectTimes": 0,
                    "correctTimes": 0,
                    "question": "3+3",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "mastery": false
                }
            ],
            "subject": "MATH"
        },
        {
            "cards": [{
                "incorrectTimes": 0,
                "correctTimes": 0,
                "question": "g",
                "answer": "9.8",
                "mastery": false
            }],
            "subject": "Physics"
        }
    ]
}